Guide to the Claudia Kolker Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Journalism, id164600
  - Freelance Work, id164676
    - “Congress’s trading cards have no gum”, News Journal, Mansfield, OH, October 1989; id164830 (Ovsbox 9, Item 20)
    - “Kohl’s bills on Chinese students, germ warfare pass”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164831 (Ovsbox 9, Item 21)
    - “Bill includes Wisconsin contracts”, Wisconsin State Journal, November 1989; id164832 (Ovsbox 9, Item 22)
    - “Aspin sees big Pentagon cuts”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164833 (Ovsbox 9, Item 23)
    - “Lawmakers want to prohibit testing for personal facts”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164834 (Ovsbox 9, Item 24)
    - “Bus-lift issue divides Rep. Petri, disabled”, Wisconsin State Journal, November 1989; id164835 (Ovsbox 9, Item 25)
    - “3 Aspins for a Coelho?: Baseball cards sport congressional faces”, Wisconsin State Journal, October 1989; id164836 (Ovsbox 9, Item 26)
    - “Kastenmeier targets health, rural issues”, Wisconsin State Journal, December 1989; id164837 (Ovsbox 9, Item 27)
    - “Congress to close campaign money loophole”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164838 (Ovsbox 9, Item 28)
    - “Gunderson carves niche in new role”, Wisconsin State Journal, November 1989; id164839 (Ovsbox 9, Item 29)
    - “Aspin: Pentagon spending may drop dramatically”, Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id164840 (Ovsbox 9, Item 30)
    - “Kasten helps out hearing impaired”, La Crosse Tribune, September 1989; id164841 (Ovsbox 9, Item 31)
    - “State’s lawmakers see opportunities and risks”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164842 (Ovsbox 9, Item 32)
    - “Aspin urging U.S. caution in East German upheaval”, Wisconsin State Journal, November 1989; id164843 (Ovsbox 9, Item 33)
    - “Defense bill should boost state economy”, Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id164844 (Ovsbox 9, Item 34)
    - “Chippewa leaders visit bureaucrats”, Sheboygan Press, May 1989; id164845 (Ovsbox 9, Item 35)
    - Page 4A, The Journal Times, May 1989; id164846 (Ovsbox 9, Item 36)
    - "U.S. Senate gets deaf Americans’ message", Wisconsin State Journal, November 1989; id164847 (Ovsbox 9, Item 37)
    - “Disclosure forms outline congressmen’s honoraria”, La Crosse Tribune, May 1989; id164848 (Ovsbox 9, Item 38)
    - “Lawmakers would shun excess in campaign fund”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164849 (Ovsbox 9, Item 39)
    - “Kastenmeier decries laws attributed to ‘Red Scare’”, The Journal Times, May 1989; id164850 (Ovsbox 9, Item 40)
    - “Laws repressive, Kastenmeier says”, La Crosse Tribune, May 1989; id164851 (Ovsbox 9, Item 41)
    - “Plan of attack reached on spearing”, The Journal Times, May 1989; id164852 (Ovsbox 9, Item 42)
    - “Kasten meets with deaf state students at Gallaudet”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164853 (Ovsbox 9, Item 43)
    - “Kohl labeled ‘model senator’ on investments”, La Crosse Tribune, August 1989; id164854 (Ovsbox 9, Item 44)
    - “Anti-poverty plan sought”, Wisconsin State Journal, September 1989; id164855 (Ovsbox 9, Item 45)
    - “State scholars: Amendment not needed to protect flag”, La Crosse Tribune, September 1989; id164856 (Ovsbox 9, Item 46)
    - “Hearing impaired get helping hand”, The Journal Times, September 1989; id164857 (Ovsbox 9, Item 47)
    - “Inouye assured Chippewa on rights”, Wisconsin State Journal, May 1989; id164858 (Ovsbox 9, Item 48)
    - “Drug selling rising in area: More being prosecuted on drug charges, report says”, La Crosse Tribune, September 1989; id164859 (Ovsbox 9, Item 49)
    - “Lab-derived product might win support from activists”, Appeal-Democrat, March 1990; id164860 (Ovsbox 9, Item 50)
    - “State delegation uses recess for talks, visiting constituents”, Wisconsin State Journal, August 1989; id164861 (Ovsbox 9, Item 51)
    - “Environmentalists want cleanup plan strengthened”, The Sheboygan Press, March 1990; id164862 (Ovsbox 9, Item 52)
    - “Hanaway satisfied with efforts to combat drugs”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id164863 (Ovsbox 9, Item 53)
    - “Petri Sensenbrenner support Bush’s veto”, The Sheboygan Press, January 1990; id164864 (Ovsbox 9, Item 54)
    - “Inouye missed 1st invitations from Thompson”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1990; id164865 (Ovsbox 9, Item 55)
    - “School trains students for a career on the Hill”, Wisconsin State Journal, December 1989; id164866 (Ovsbox 9, Item 56)
    - “Kasten’s welcome wagon assists foreign politicians”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1990; id164867 (Ovsbox 9, Item 57)
    - “Engeleiter endorses Bush wage plan”, The Journal Times, September 1989; id164868 (Ovsbox 9, Item 58)
    - “State farmers selected from test: Improved water to be long-term result”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id164869 (Ovsbox 9, Item 59)
    - “Inouye sees solution on treaty rights”, The Journal Times, December 1989; id164870 (Ovsbox 9, Item 60)
    - “State loses federal grant dollars”, The Journal Times, December 1989; id164871 (Ovsbox 9, Item 61)
    - “Aspin, Kleczka vote the least”, Wisconsin State Journal, December 1989; id164872 (Ovsbox 9, Item 62)
    - “Armenian genocide bill loses Kasten’s backing”, Wisconsin State Journal, December 1989; id164873 (Ovsbox 9, Item 63)
    - “Lawmakers blast Bush’s Chinese visa veto”, The Journal Times, December 1989; id164874 (Ovsbox 9, Item 64)
    - “Bills aid Chinese students, halt weapons”, The Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id164875 (Ovsbox 9, Item 65)
    - “Wisconsin congressmen disappointed by Chippewa’s rejection of treaty pact”, The Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id164876 (Ovsbox 9, Item 66)
    - “Defense bill has opportunities for Wisconsin”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164877 (Ovsbox 9, Item 67)
    - “Soviet defense exchange possible”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164878 (Ovsbox 9, Item 68)
    - “Heating-aid cuts could leave poor in cold”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id164879 (Ovsbox 9, Item 69)
    - “Opponents say Kasten unrealistic”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164880 (Ovsbox 9, Item 70)
    - “Poor to suffer if heating aid is cut”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164881 (Ovsbox 9, Item 71)
    - “Inouye opposes federal spearing aid, Obey says”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id164882 (Ovsbox 9, Item 72)
    - “Tax credit tops Petri’s list of goals”, The Sheboygan Press, January 1990; id164883 (Ovsbox 9, Item 73)
    - “Kasten proposes cut in payroll tax”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164884 (Ovsbox 9, Item 74)
    - “UW-L graduate hoped for override”, La Crosse Tribune, January 1990; id164885 (Ovsbox 9, Item 75)
    - “Government urged to buy forest land”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164886 (Ovsbox 9, Item 76)
    - “’91 budget holds news for farmers”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164887 (Ovsbox 9, Item 77)
    - “While other bases shut down, McCoy may get $26 million”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164888 (Ovsbox 9, Item 78)
    - “Kasten, Kohl opposed China veto”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164889 (Ovsbox 9, Item 79)
    - “BGH: Dairy dream or nightmare?”, The Journal Times, February 1990; id164890 (Ovsbox 9, Item 80)
    - “President’s speech evaluated”, The Sheboygan Press, February 1990; id164891 (Ovsbox 9, Item 81)
    - “Kohl pushes for gun-free school zones”, LaCrosse Tribune, February 1990; id164892 (Ovsbox 9, Item 82)
    - “Kastenmeier opposed Bush on most votes”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164893 (Ovsbox 9, Item 83)
    - “Soglin’s ‘peace dividend’ gains at mayor meeting’”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164894 (Ovsbox 9, Item 84)
    - “Sturtevant, Army will discuss Reserve center”, The Journal Times, Janaury 1990; id164895 (Ovsbox 9, Item 85)
    - “Kastenmeier, Bush on opposite sides”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164896 (Ovsbox 9, Item 86)
    - “SBA Plans to build jobs in rural areas”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164897 (Ovsbox 9, Item 87)
    - “State lawmakers back House override of veto”, La Crosse Tribune, January 1990; id164898 (Ovsbox 9, Item 88)
    - “Extra aid not enough for county”, La Crosse Tribune, January 1990; id164899 (Ovsbox 9, Item 89)
    - “Nelson: Bush is better”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164900 (Ovsbox 9, Item 90)
    - “Aspin part of group slated to visit Panama”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164901 (Ovsbox 9, Item 91)
    - “Waste firm kicks in for nature group”, Wisconsin State Journal, January 1990; id164902 (Ovsbox 9, Item 92)
    - “Monument at Capital to honor police who were slain on duty”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id164903 (Ovsbox 9, Item 93)
    - “Thompson: Acid rain producing states should pay”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164904 (Ovsbox 9, Item 94)
    - “Modine working on helium-cooled air conditioner”, The Journal Times, January 1990; id164905 (Ovsbox 9, Item 95)
    - “Study finds fewer minorities get adequate prenatal care”, Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id164906 (Ovsbox 9, Item 96)
    - “Congressmen bound for Israel”, La Crosse Tribune, December 1989; id164907 (Ovsbox 9, Item 97)
    - “Drop in price supports could hurt dairy industry”, The Journal Times, December 1989; id164908 (Ovsbox 9, Item 98)
    - “State delegation leans to approval”, Wisconsin State Journal, December 1989; id164909 (Ovsbox 9, Item 99)
    - “Study: U.S. grants to state dip”, Wisconsin State Journal, December 1989; id164910 (Ovsbox 9, Item 100)
    - “State delegation supports closing war-chest loophole”, Wisconsin State Journal, November 1989; id164911 (Ovsbox 9, Item 101)
    - “Lawmakers from state rate Bush”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id164912 (Ovsbox 9, Item 102)
    - “Engeleiter backs Bush wage plan”, Wisconsin State Journal, September 1989; id164913 (Ovsbox 9, Item 103)
    - “Lawmakers get ‘baseball cards’”, The News-Herald, October 1989; id164914 (Ovsbox 9, Item 104)
    - “Inouye touts treaty panel, study of fish”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1990; id164915 (Ovsbox 9, Item 105)
    - “D.C. fielding treaty issues”, The Journal Times, April 1990; id164916 (Ovsbox 9, Item 106)
    - “House panel backs ’90 farm bill dairy section”, The Sheboygan Press, April 1990; id164917 (Ovsbox 9, Item 107)
    - “Speller makes good show”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164918 (Ovsbox 9, Item 108)
    - “Capital keeps North Woods watch”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1990; id164919 (Ovsbox 9, Item 109)
    - “Southern Voting is Scrutinized: Region’s Voters Are Fleeing Democrat Fold”, The Commercial Dispatch, February 1989; id164920 (Ovsbox 9, Item 110)
    - “Aspin skips closing days of Congress”, La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id164921 (Ovsbox 9, Item 111)
    - “State girl enjoying spelling perquisites”, Wisconsin State Journal, May 1989; id164922 (Ovsbox 9, Item 112)
    - Page A26, The Washington Post, November 1989; id164923 (Ovsbox 9, Item 113)
    - “State girl is letter-perfect on first day of spelling bee”, The Journal Times, June 1989; id164924 (Ovsbox 9, Item 114)
    - “State spelling champ falls in fourth round”, The Journal Times, June 1989; id164925 (Ovsbox 9, Item 115)
    - “Oshkosh Truck still uncertain on contract”, Wisconsin State Journal, July 1989; id164926 (Ovsbox 9, Item 116)
    - “Kasten fights mail-order tax”, La Crosse Tribune, May 1989; id164927 (Ovsbox 9, Item 117)
    - “Germ warfare target of Kohl bill”, La Crosse Tribune, May 1989; id164928 (Ovsbox 9, Item 118)
    - “Kohl remains adamant in opposing U.S. budget”, Sheboygan Press, May 1989; id164929 (Ovsbox 9, Item 119)
    - “Washington abuzz with nation’s top spellers”, The Journal Times, May 1989; id164930 (Ovsbox 9, Item 120)
    - “Kasten, Kohl release financial disclosure statements”, The Journal times, May 1989; id164931 (Ovsbox 9, Item 121)
    - “Kohl battling $1 trillion budget proposal”, La Crosse Tribune, May 1989; id164932 (Ovsbox 9, Item 122)
    - “Kohl fights budget”, Wisconsin State Journal, May 1989; id164933 (Ovsbox 9, Item 123)
    - “Kohl bucks party leaders on budget”, The Journal Times, May 1989; id164934 (Ovsbox 9, Item 124)
    - “Aspin loss, Oshkosh gain?”, The Journal Times, June 1989; id164935 (Ovsbox 9, Item 125)
    - “Area hospitals meet Medicare standard”, Sheboygan Press, December 1989; id164936 (Ovsbox 9, Item 126)
    - “Tougher clean-air bill urged”, La Crosse Tribune, June 1989; id164937 (Ovsbox 9, Item 127)
    - “State groups join clean air petition”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164938 (Ovsbox 9, Item 128)
    - “Aspin says upgrade of ICBMs up to president”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164939 (Ovsbox 9, Item 129)
    - “Thompson praises plan for clean air”, The Journal Times, June 1989; id164940 (Ovsbox 9, Item 130)
    - “Sale of surplus butter to Soviets gets go ahead”, La Crosse Tribune, June 1989; id164941 (Ovsbox 9, Item 131)
    - “Spahn makes his pitch for old-timers”, The Journal Times, June 1989; id164942 (Ovsbox 9, Item 132)
    - “Kasten has hopes for Soviet Union”, The Journal Times, June 1989; id164943 (Ovsbox 9, Item 133)
    - “Response mixed on amendment”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164944 (Ovsbox 9, Item 134)
    - “Lawmakers differ on flag amendment”, The Sheboygan Press, June 1989; id164945 (Ovsbox 9, Item 135)
    - “Visiting Kasten impressed by openness of Soviets”, Wisconsin State Journal, June 1989; id164946 (Ovsbox 9, Item 136)
    - “Organic farming gaining momentum”, The Sheboygan Press, July 1989; id164947 (Ovsbox 9, Item 137)
    - “Aspin has taxpayers to thank for trips”, The Journal Times, July 1989; id164948 (Ovsbox 9, Item 138)
    - “One-year visa extensions available for China students”, Wisconsin State Journal, July 1989; id164949 (Ovsbox 9, Item 139)
    - “Kastenmeier defends vote against cut in arts funding”, Wisconsin State Journal, July 1989; id164950 (Ovsbox 9, Item 140)
    - “Kastenmeier brushes away attack by official over vote for arts funds”, Sheboygan Press, July 1989; id164951 (Ovsbox 9, Item 141)
    - “Visa extensions put in motion for Chinese”, The Journal Times, July 1989; id164952 (Ovsbox 9, Item 142)
    - “Provision in Bush’s clean air plan a setback to Wisconsin: Kasten”, The Sheboygan Press, July 1989; id164953 (Ovsbox 9, Item 143)
    - “Plan could raise environmental tensions”, The Journal Times, July 1989; id164954 (Ovsbox 9, Item 144)
    - “Some urge U.S. to get tough, others disagree”, Wisconsin State Journal, August 1989; id164955 (Ovsbox 9, Item 145)
    - “Inside look; Kohler native has a different view of Washington”, Sheboygan Press, July 1989; id164956 (Ovsbox 9, Item 146)
    - “State’s delegation ponders proper response to captive’s execution”, The Journal Times, August 1989; id164957 (Ovsbox 9, Item 147)
    - “Congress urged to spend more on drug-addicted newborns, mothers”, Sheboygan Press, August 1989; id164958 (Ovsbox 9, Item 148)
    - “Aspin joins UAW seeking Kenosha aid”, Wisconsin State Journal, August 1989; id164959 (Ovsbox 9, Item 149)
    - “State work-leave law generous”, Wisconsin State Journal, August 1989; id164960 (Ovsbox 9, Item 150)
    - “Kasten, Obey split on debt swap plan”, Wisconsin State Journal, August 1989; id164961 (Ovsbox 9, Item 151)
    - “Family leave law among best”, La Crosse Tribune, August 1989; id164962 (Ovsbox 9, Item 152)
    - “Kohl has divested holdings in S. Africa; Kasten hasn’t”, Wisconsin State Journal, August 1989; id164963 (Ovsbox 9, Item 153)
    - “Sensenbrenner in Japan forum”, The Sheboygan Press, August 1989; id164964 (Ovsbox 9, Item 154)
    - “Federal court reforms pushed”, The Journal Times, April 1990; id164965 (Ovsbox 9, Item 155)
    - “Bill would ease citizenship requirements for Hmong”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1990; id164966 (Ovsbox 9, Item 156)
    - “Conservation ethic missing, Nelson says”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1990; id164967 (Ovsbox 9, Item 157)
    - “USDA planning to conduct hearings on milk pricing”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1990; id164968 (Ovsbox 9, Item 158)
    - “Bill raises guaranteed price for dairy products”, The Journal Times, April 1990; id164969 (Ovsbox 9, Item 159)
    - “Thompson wins praise at Senate hearing”, The Journal Times, April 1990; id164970 (Ovsbox 9, Item 160)
    - “Senate panel approves Thompson for Amtrack”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1990; id164971 (Ovsbox 9, Item 161)
    - “State is among leaders in chemical-free farming”, La Crosse Tribune, July 1989; id164972 (Ovsbox 9, Item 162)
    - “Gingrich, Gunderson to team up”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1989; id164973 (Ovsbox 9, Item 163)
    - Page A1, Washington State Journal, April 1989; id164974 (Ovsbox 9, Item 164)
    - “Bill gives homebuyers break”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1989; id164975 (Ovsbox 9, Item 165)
    - “Weather station may be phased out”, Sheboygan Press, March 1989; id164976 (Ovsbox 9, Item 166)
    - “Biotechnology control bills introduced”, Sheboygan Press, March 1989; id164977 (Ovsbox 9, Item 167)
    - “Engeleiter hearing to begin next week”, The Journal Times, April 1989; id164978 (Ovsbox 9, Item 168)
    - “Wisconsin activists lend their support”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1989; id164979 (Ovsbox 9, Item 169)
    - “Petri pushes plan for line-item veto”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1989; id164980 (Ovsbox 9, Item 170)
    - “Lawmakers take abortion stance”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1989; id164981 (Ovsbox 9, Item 171)
    - “State’s Mother-Infant Health Care Record Among Worst”, The Commercial Dispatch, March 1989; id164982 (Ovsbox 9, Item 172)
    - “Lawmakers take abortion stands”, The Journal Times, April 1989; id164983 (Ovsbox 9, Item 173)
    - “Why state gets little fed money”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1989; id164984 (Ovsbox 9, Item 174)
    - “Engeleiter wins committee endorsement”, Sheboygan Press, April 1989; id164985 (Ovsbox 9, Item 175)
    - “Gingrich rewards Gunderson”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1989; id164986 (Ovsbox 9, Item 176)
    - “Mr. Smith returns to Washington”, Sheboygan Press, April 1989; id164987 (Ovsbox 9, Item 177)
    - “Environmentalists note Earth Day”, The Journal Times, April 1989; id164988 (Ovsbox 9, Item 178)
    - “Petri worked on lengthy probe of Wright”, Sheboygan Press, April 1989; id164989 (Ovsbox 9, Item 179)
    - “Petri likens Wright probe to sacrifices of jury duty”, Wisconsin State Journal, April 1989; id164990 (Ovsbox 9, Item 180)
    - “Lawmakers join debate over abortion”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1989; id164991 (Ovsbox 9, Item 181)
    - “Rep. Aspin open-minded on cuts”, Sheboygan Press, April 1989; id164992 (Ovsbox 9, Item 182)
    - “Honorariums are kept by U.S. lawmakers”, Wisconsin State Journal, March 1989; id164993 (Ovsbox 9, Item 183)
    - “State ranks third from bottom in federal spending”, The Journal Times, April 1989; id164994 (Ovsbox 9, Item 184)
    - “Kasten tells new ‘Coalition To Stamp Out The Abuse Tax’”; Sheboygan Press, May 1989; id164995 (Ovsbox 9, Item 185)
    - “Kasten leads push to alter tax law”, La Crosse Tribune, April 1989; id164996 (Ovsbox 9, Item 186)
    - Classified page from the Sheboygan Press, March 1989; id164997 (Ovsbox 9, Item 187)
    - “Confirmation hearings set for Sen. Engeleiter”, La Crosse Tribune, March 1989; id164998 (Ovsbox 9, Item 188)
    - “Gunderson named deputy House whip”, Sheboygan Press, April 1989; id164999 (Ovsbox 9, Item 189)
    - Page 5A, The Commercial Dispatch, February 1989; id165000 (Ovsbox 9, Item 190)
    - “Low-Income Families Urged to File Tax Returns”, The Commercial Dispatch, March 1989; id165001 (Ovsbox 9, Item 191)
    - “USDA sets national hearings on milk pricing”, The Journal Times, March 1990; id165002 (Ovsbox 9, Item 192)
    - “Thompson likes Bush’s air cleanup plan”, Sheboygan Press, June 1989; id165003 (Ovsbox 9, Item 193)
    - “UW officials lobby to end anti-gay rule”, Wisconsin State Journal, February 1990; id165004 (Ovsbox 9, Item 194)
    - “Shaw lobbies opening military to homosexuals”, Sheboygan Press, February 1990; id165005 (Ovsbox 9, Item 195)
    - “Report: Prenatal care inadequate”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id165006 (Ovsbox 9, Item 196)
    - “Kasten, Kohl both praise repeal of ‘89’”, Sheboygan Press, November 1989; id165007 (Ovsbox 9, Item 197)
    - Page A-8 of La Crosse Tribune, November 1989; id165008 (Ovsbox 9, Item 198)
    - “Health provision repeal approved by legislators”, The Journal Times, November 1989; id165009 (Ovsbox 9, Item 199)
    - Article from O (Oprah) Magazine, November 2003; id165010 (Ovsbox 10, Item 1)
    - “Head of the Class: 24-Year-Old Design Prodigy Victor Conejo Brings Stetson Hats Back into the Ring”, Los Angeles Times Magazine, January 2002; id165011 (Ovsbox 10, Item 2)
    - “Zoot Me Up!”, Houston Press Magazine, February 1996; id165012 (Ovsbox 10, Item 3)
    - “Radio Sweetheart”, Houston Press Magazine, February 1996; id165013 (Ovsbox 10, Item 4)
    - “Little Osama: How the murder of a Muslim boy in Houston fanned the flames of anti-Americanism in Pakistan”, Salon, March 2003; id165014 (Ovsbox 10, Item 5)
    - “A City’s Buried Shame: Tulsa’s long cover-up of a horrific 1921 race riot prompts a search for a mass grave”, Los Angeles Times, October 1999; id165015 (Ovsbox 10, Item 6)
    - “Dancing for Pay, Dying by the Hand of a Demon: At clubs where lonely Latino men seek solace, dark legend surround 2 women’s deaths in Texas”, Los Angeles Times, July 1999; id165016 (Ovsbox 10, Item 7)
    - “Death Penalty Moratorium Idea Attracts Even Conservatives”, Los Angeles Times, August 2000; id165017 (Ovsbox 10, Item 8)
    - “KPEN: Houston’s public radio for inmates”, San Antonio Current, November 2002; id165018 (Ovsbox 10, Item 9)
    - “South Asia’s Dance of War”, Times, January 2002; id165019 (Ovsbox 10, Item 10)
    - “Flexible foot works a low-tech miracle: Half a million in Asia benefitting”, Houston Chronicle, December 2002; id165020 (Ovsbox 10, Item 11)
    - “African immigrants turn to traditional leaders for guidance”, Houston Chronicle, undated; id165021 (Ovsbox 10, Item 12)
    - “Casualties of War: Houston’s Vietnamese now call Texas home, but they continue to be haunted by ghosts of the conflict that drove them here”, Houston Press, February 1995; id165022 (Ovsbox 10, Item 13)
    - “Proud to Call Their Own: Okinawa breaks from influence of mainland”, Houston Chronicle, February 1998; id165023 (Ovsbox 10, Item 14)
    - “How Low Can You Go?”, Houston Press, November 1995; id165024 (Ovsbox 10, Item 15)
    - “A Sense of Placement”, Houston Press, April 1996; id165025 (Ovsbox 10, Item 16)
    - “Jasper Sheriff Battled Ghosts of East Texas”, Los Angeles Times, February 1999; id165026 (Ovsbox 10, Item 17)
    - “The Battle Over Brentwood”, Houston Press, March 1995; id165027 (Ovsbox 10, Item 18)
    - “Mushroom Trip: A search for wild edible shrooms”, undated; id165028 (Ovsbox 10, Item 19)
    - “The invisible girl”; Houston Press, May 1996; id165029 (Ovsbox 10, Item 20)
    - “Sons of San Juan: Salvadorans find solace in numbers”, Houston Chronicle, undated; id165030 (Ovsbox 10, Item 21)
    - “A Delicate Healing: The mercury-poisoned waters of Minamata unleashed a sickness not only of body but of society’s fabric”, Houston Chronicle, February 1998; id165031 (Ovsbox 10, Item 22)
    - “Bush’s Texas Traits Don’t Rope In All”, Los Angeles Times, 2000; id165032 (Ovsbox 10, Item 23)
    - “A Painful Present as Historians Confront a Nation’s Bloody Past”, Los Angeles Times, February 2000; id165033 (Ovsbox 10, Item 24)
    - “Roots of discontent: Dead Enron power plant affecting environment, economy and livelihoods in India”, Houston Chronicle, undated; id165034 (Ovsbox 10, Item 25)
    - “1 Killing but Many Victms: Ex-DEA Phil Jordan sees drugs lords’ hands in his brother’s slaying and related misfortunes”, Los Angeles Times, July 2000; id165035 (Ovsbox 10, Item 26)
    - “Let Us Pray”; Houston Press, September 1995; id165036 (Ovsbox 10, Item 27)